[
  {
    "id": "01",
    "question": "What is the fullform of DOM?",
    "options": [
      "Document Object Model",
      "Document Objective Model",
      "Document On Model",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Document Object Model"
  },
  {
    "id": "02",
    "question": "What is JSX in ReactJS?",
    "options": [
      "A state management library",
      "An HTML file",
      "A syntax extension for JavaScript",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "A syntax extension for JavaScript"
  },
  {
    "id": "03",
    "question": "In React, what is used to pass data to a component from outside?",
    "options": ["SetState", "Props", "State", "Hooks"],
    "answer": "Props"
  },
  {
    "id": "04",
    "question": "What is the purpose of the setState method in React?",
    "options": [
      "To update the component’s state",
      "To force re-rendering of a component",
      "To set initial state",
      "To access the DOM"
    ],
    "answer": "To update the component’s state"
  },
  {
    "id": "05",
    "question": "What of the following is used in React.js to increase performance?",
    "options": [
      "Original DOM",
      "Virtual DOM",
      "Both A and B.",
      "None of the above."
    ],
    "answer": "Virtual DOM"
  },
  {
    "id": "06",
    "question": "What is the default port where webpack-server runs?",
    "options": ["3000", "8080", "3030", "6060"],
    "answer": "3000"
  },
  {
    "id": "07",
    "question": "How many numbers of elements a valid react component can return?",
    "options": ["1", "2", "3", "Unlimited"],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "08",
    "question": "What is the declarative way to render a dynamic list of components based on values in an array?",
    "options": [
      "Using the reduce array method",
      "Using the <Each /> component",
      "Using the Array.map() method",
      "With a for/while loop"
    ],
    "answer": "Using the Array.map() method"
  },
  {
    "id": "09",
    "question": "What is a state in React?",
    "options": [
      "A permanent storage.",
      "Internal storage of the component.",
      "External storage of the component.",
      "None of the above."
    ],
    "answer": "Internal storage of the component."
  },
  {
    "id": "10",
    "question": "What are the two ways to handle data in React?",
    "options": [
      "State & Props",
      "Services & Components",
      "State & Services",
      "State & Component"
    ],
    "answer": "State & Props"
  }
]
